[Music]
Billionaire Alliance with a master plan.
Twitter tycoon and the orange tiny man
dismantling the system with their golden
wrench.
Democracies just collateral in their
power trench.
Public servants tossed aside like
yesterday's trash. Programs frozen with
a bureaucratic crash. They're selling us
a future build up quicks and lies. We're
waving flags and feeding us in disguise.
The seeds on fire going up in flames.
Billionaires and tyrants playing power
games. They're cutting institutions.
One by one they fall. While we stand
here watching as they tear down it all.
Tear it down. Tear it down. Watch it
burn to the ground.
Federal workers shown the door without a
care.
Budget freezes leaving families in
despair.
Department disappearing overnight.
Rewritten just to serve the right.
They're deleting fashion, changing what
we see, rewriting web pages of our
history. The truth gets buried under
corporate lies as the last checks and
balances slowly die.
[Music]
Democracies on fire, going up in flames.
Billionaires and tyres playing power
games. They're cutting institutions.
One by one they fall. While we stand
here watching as they tear down it all.
Tear it down. Tear it down. Watch it
burn to the ground.
[Music]